<resources>
    <string name="app_name">JEMTEC</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Drawer Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_jemtec">About JEMTEC</string>
    <string name="frag_1">About JEMTEC</string>
    <string name="abt_jim"><![CDATA[JIMS Engineering Management Technical Campus at Greater Noida is one of the Best Engineering Colleges in entire Delhi & NCR.It is approved by AICTE and Affiliated to GGSIPU,Delhi(an A Grade Uninversity accredited by NAAC ).\nThe Institute was established in the year 2008 with a mission to provide high quality education in the field of Engineering & Management and to develop and train the next generation technocrats & business leaders.It offers a holistic and harmonized training programme with strong academics, personality development, cultural and sports activities and provides an inspiring learning environnment which transnforms the young students into talented
professionals.\nThe Institute has qualified and experienced faculty.It also has strong interface with industry which enables it to expose students to guest speakers from Corporate World, Industry visits and seek opportunities, to execute live projects in top industrial organisations.]]></string>
     <string name="vis">Vision\n\nWe visualize that JIMS will evolve in the future as\nan Institute of high academic learning, known for its total commitment to excellence in management and technical education and research with a holi-\nstic concern for quality of life ,environment ,soci-\nety and ethics.
</string>
    <string name="misn">Mission\n\nTo serve society and improve the quality of life by imparting high quality education in Management\nand Engineering, providing training and developm-\nent services, fostering research, giving consultan-\ncy services to industry and disseminating informa-\ntion through publication of books, journals and ma-\ngazines.</string>
    <string name="chair_msg"> \t\t\t\t\t\tDr.Amit Gupta\n\t\t\t\t\t\tMasters in International Business\n\t\t\t\t\t\tB.Com(SRCC)\nThe institute was founded in 2008 with a clear vision and purpose It was envisioned that in a foreseeable future it would evolve into a world class institution recognized for its commitment to high powered quality education and research.We have also committed ourselves to developing outstanding professionals and entrepreneurs who exemplify humanistic value, are socially responsible stewards and create and disseminate practitioner oriented knowledge thatwill uplift society.\n In order to keep pace with the velocity of change and thrive in an uncertain environment our institute has already shifted gears to a mode of mastering change. It has launched several strategic initiatives both at the macro and micro levels to ensure that students overall development is in tune with the present demands and expectation of industry. Our strategic focus in future will address areas of curriculum design,mentoring and live projects,advanced statistical software training, international summer internships, soft skills, stress coping and E learning.These initiatives will focus on developing student competencies in dealing with global complexity, emerging technologies and change,and social and cultural diversity.\n\n I am confident that our“high value adding”initiatives will help to create skilled leaders of tomorrow as value is all about upskilling individuals and contributing to business results. Wishing you all the best for a bright future.</string>
    <string name="dir_msg">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tProf.(Dr)Rajan Anand Malik\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tB.E,M.Tech,MBA,PhD\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tDirector\nJIMS EngineeringManagementTechnical Campus (JEMTEC) is poised to achieve excellence in professional learning and to acquire a unique status in the National Region (NCR) by synergizing theoretical knowledge and practical skills to provide professional competence and produce professionals of national and international acclaim, who will be recognized as a product of a top ranking Institution imparting high quality education.\n\n The underlying force in JEMTEC is the right blend of excellence of faculty, dedication of staff and the interest and the support of management of Jagannath Gupta Memorial Educational Society. I wish to express my sincere greetings to all the students who are aspiring to join JEMTEC and take this opportunity to assure them that the experience that they would gain while studying at JEMTEC would be lifelong for learning and development. I expect that the high quality of knowledge and skills imparted during their stay will help them to develop as valued assets for industry and diverse professional fields, thereby achieving the pinnacle of success.</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="mgmt_quota">• A candidate must satisfy eligibility criteria and obtain qualifying IPUCET Rank.\n• According to GGSIPU 2016 Admission Brochure: “85% of the sanctioned intake shall be allocated for Delhi Region and 15% of the sanctioned intake shall be allocated for the outside Delhi Region. However in case of Self financing Institutes sanctioned intake also includes 10% management quota seats (if offered)." \n• Please note that through management quota, the admission fees, etc. will be higher than what other students have had to pay.\n• Admission Helpline Numbers: 0120–3819700 / 01 / 04 / 05, 0120–6587569</string>
    <string name="documnt_rq">1) 10th class mark sheet (original + 2 photo copy)\n2) 10th class passing certificate (original + 2 photocopy)\n3) 12th class Mark sheet (original + 2 photocopy)\n4) 12th class passing certificate, if available (original + 2 photocopy)\n5) character certificate (original)\n6) medical certificate\n7) Your IPU CET Admit card (original)\n8) Your Drafts\n9) Verification form\n10) Preference Sheet\n11) Caste Certificate (if not general) (original + 2 photocopy) In the case of Sikh minority, the format as prescribed by Delhi Sikh Gurudwara Management Committee .\n12) Affidavit on non-judicial stamp paper of Rs.10/ - for seeking provisional admission in case the result of qualifying examination is yet to be declared.\nNOTE :-The Original Certificates (except the admit card, medical certificate and Character Certificate) will be returned to the candidates after verification. The photocopies of these certificates, Admit card (in original), Medical certificate (in original) and Character Certificate (in original) shall be retained.</string>
    <string name="title_3">Documents\nRequired</string>
    <string name="ipt">IPUCET</string>
    <string name="mgmt">Management Quota</string>
    <string name="ipc"> <u>IPU Counselling</u>\nStudents must note that only those students, who have qualified in IPU CET 2015, can apply for the IPU CET 2015 Counseling. Candidates can check the IPU CET Counseling Procedure and the counselling Schedules for B.Tech at techbits.co.in . IPU CET 2015 Counselling Details:\n Registration:\n 1. Counselling Fee Payment: \n IPU CET 2015 Registration Fees: Rs.1000 (non refundable)\n IPU CET 2015 Payment mode: \n1. Net banking\n 2. Credit/Debit Card\n 3. Candidates can download and print the Indian Bank Challan. (Registration will be only done two days after the payment is made) \nCash payment has to be made by the candidate at any Indian Bank branch.\n Note: The Bank Challan copy has to be kept for further reference.\n\n IPU CET 2015 Registration Form: \n1)Candidates can log in entering their IPU CET 2015 Roll Number, Date of Birth and Mobile Number.\n2) Candidates have to fill in the Bank Reference no (transaction ID/Challan No.) in the online form after payment of the registration fees.\n3) After authentication, candidates will have to fill in their particulars- personal, academic, contact details with address, mobile No. and Email ID.\n4) They must choose a password as per specifications mentioned therein.\n\n Choice Filling: \n1)Candidates must log in using their course, CET 2015 Roll No. and password chosen during registration.\n2) Candidates must fill their choices as per their course preferences.\n3) They must fill the maximum number of options to ensure that they avail a seat of their preference.\n4) There is no restriction on the number of options that can be filled by a candidate.\n Verification of Documents:</string>

</resources>
